sounddogs.com 2012-12-19

# Sounddogs.com Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by Sounddogs.com, Inc.. (Sounddogs.com includes all Web sites and other Internet media properties.)  
The following discloses our Privacy Policy.

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**  
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" (IP) address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within Sounddogs.com, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our Web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors.

**What are cookies?**  
From time to time, Sounddogs.com may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.

Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of Sounddogs.com's Web sites you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. We may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our Sites. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

**What other information do you request?**  
We may also request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists or information about seminars). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy which means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent.

In addition, Sounddogs.com will not send you junk email, however we may send up to two emails per year announcing new Sounddogs.com products and services. If you have opt-in subscribed to our email news list you may receive one email approximately per month. When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

**What information do you collect when I purchase something?**  
If you are purchasing something from a Sounddogs.com media property we need to know your name, e-mail address, billing and shipping address, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information may also be used by us to notify you of related product and services, but will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose.

Certain Sounddogs.com media properties use a shopping cart feature that safeguards this information by using industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted servers. SSL codes the information transferred between you and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information. Other Sounddogs.com media properties do not use SSL and thereby do not offer a secure coded way to transfer information, although is typical in cases of non-critical information.

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**  
Sounddogs.com will disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

1) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on Sounddogs.com,

2) Protect and defend the rights or property of Sounddogs.com sites, or visitors to Sounddogs.com,

3) Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties,

4) Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

Sounddogs.com uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. Sounddogs.com reserves the right to transfer information in connection with the sale of all or part of Sounddogs.com's capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties which receive the information. Sounddogs.com also links to a wide variety of other sites and contains advertisements of third parties. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. See below.

**What else should I know about my privacy when online?**  
Sounddogs.com Web sites contains many links to other Web sites. Sounddogs.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Sounddogs.com does not share any of the individual personal information you provide Sounddogs.com with the sites to which Sounddogs.com links, although Sounddogs.com may share aggregate data with such Web sites (such as how many people use our Site).

Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

**Your Consent To This Agreement**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Sounddogs.com as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Sounddogs and SoundStorm are registered trademarks of Sounddogs.com, Inc. in the United States.  
Oscar and Academy Awards are registered trademark and service marks of the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences. All other trademarks contained herein are the property of their respective owners.
